Babes in Toyland is a family, fantasy, tv movie film directed by Clive Donner.
11-year-old Lisa has no time for toys; she's too busy taking
care of her siblings and cooking for her mother.
During the Christmas Eve blizzard, Lisa travels to Toyland in Wizard of
Oz-like fashion and arrives just in time for a wedding.
Young Mary Contrary is about to marry mean, old Barnaby Barnacle,
despite the fact that she loves Jack Be Nimble.
Lisa tries to stop this terrible wedding and, together with her new
friends, discovers that Barnaby wants to take over Toyland.
Lisa, Mary, Jack, and Georgie Porgie ask the Toymaster for help, but he
can't help them as long as Lisa doesn't truly believe in toys.
Lisa Piper, played by Drew Barrymore.
Barnie / Barnaby Barnicle, played by Richard Mulligan.
Mrs. Piper / Widow Hubbard, played by Eileen Brennan.
Jack Fenton / Jack-be-Nimble, played by Keanu Reeves.
The Toymaster, played by Pat Morita.
Mary Piper / Mary Contrary, played by Jill Schoelen.
Babes in Toyland is a 1986 American made-for-television Christmas musical film directed by Clive
Donner and starring Drew Barrymore, Richard Mulligan, Eileen Brennan and Keanu Reeves.
Based on the 1903 operetta of the same title by Victor Herbert and Glen MacDonough, this version
features a new score by Leslie Bricusse along with select portions of Herbert's score.
Shot on location in Munich, West Germany, in summer 1986, it was broadcast on NBC
on December 19, 1986 and released on VHS on November 21, 1992.
The film was shortened to 94 minutes for overseas theatrical release; it is this version that
received a worldwide home media release, leaving the original 145-minute cut unreleased.
The film explores themes of holiday, musical, christmas.